What am I supposed to do?
(Leonard:)Pretend I believe something I don't
when I'm with Penny?
(Howard:)Hey, I'm sure Penny fakes
all kinds of things when she's with you.
Do me a favor.
Lean over, put your head right here.
(Howard:)Let me show you another way
to look at this.
(Howard:)Here we have the universe
of all women.
Okay, these are the ones
you wanna sleep with.
(Howard:)These are the women
who believe exactly what you believe.
who would be willing to sleep with you.
(Howard:)And right there,
in the little triple intersection...
...is your ideal mate.
Odds are she's a short physicist
with low self-esteem...
...who lives in a government
research facility in China.
(Leonard:)What's your point?
(Leonard:)To keep having a sexual relationship
with Penny...
...I have to give up everything I believe in?
My intellectual integrity?
(Leonard:)The very nature of who I am?
I can't do that, Howard.
(Howard:)I respect that.